mynutrikids.com 2014-03-25

# mySchoolBucks

|  |  |   
---  
  
|  **PRIVACY POLICY**  
---  
  
Introduction    
This is the privacy policy for myschoolbucks.com (the "Site"), which is owned and operated by Heartland Payment Systems, Inc. ("We", "Us" or "Our"). We take privacy seriously and have established this privacy policy to govern the privacy of information we collect from users of and visitors to our Site. Any person who uses or visits our Site consents to this policy and agrees to be bound by it. In this policy, we describe the information that we collect, what we do with that information, with whom we share that information, and whether you can access and edit the information we have collected from you.  What Information Do We Collect?    
We collect a variety of personally identifying information from users of the Site, including their name, postal and street address (Street, City, State and Zip Code), day and evening phone numbers, and email addresses (collectively "Personal Information"). In addition, if you are using the Site to purchase products and services, we will collect certain information in order to process transactions, including your credit card number, the name on the card, expiration date, billing address (Street, City, State and Zip Code) (collectively "Payment Information"). The security code (CVV2) on the front or back of the card is not stored.

We also use "cookies" to collect information. A cookie is a piece of information sent to your browser by our Web server. The browser then returns certain information to our Web server. For each visitor to our Site, our Web server automatically recognizes the consumer's domain name and email address (where possible). We also collect the domain name and email address (where possible) of visitors to our Web pages, the email addresses of those who communicate with us via email, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, and user-specific information on what pages consumers access or visit.

We also collect other information that is volunteered by our users from time to time, such as in response to surveys, polls or questionnaires and/or Site registration forms. Such information may include information about the user's personal preferences, buying habits, and opinions in addition to other information. 

How Do We Use the Information We Collect?    
The information we collect is used primarily to process transactions over the Site and to communicate with you regarding such transactions and our products and services. We also use the information to improve the content of our Site and the products and services offered on the Site, to customize the content and/or layout of our pages for each individual visitor, and to notify you about updates to our Site.

With respect to cookies: we use cookies to store visitor preferences, record session information, such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, alert visitors to new areas that we think might be of interest to them when they return to our site, record past activity at a site in order to provide better service when visitors return to our site, and customize Web page content based on visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends. 

Do We Share the Information With Third Parties?    
Information collected by us will not be shared with any third parties except as follows:

1\. We may share information with agents or contractors who assist in providing support for our internal operations; 

2\. We may disclose information when legally required to do so, at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our Site and applicable laws or to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our Site; and 

3\. We may disclose information to a successor entity in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, sale of assets or other corporate change respecting the Site.

With respect to Ad Servers: To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we may allow to place ads that may viewed on our Web pages after you've completed the registration process. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. 

Disclaimer    
We are not responsible for the acts or omissions of third parties with whom we may share information under this policy. This Site may also contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for the acts or omissions of such third-party sites and encourage you to review their privacy policies before providing any information to them.  Changes to Policy    
From time to time, we may change or amend our privacy policy. If we change our privacy policy, we will post the policy changes to our Site to notify you of these changes and we will apply the changed policy to all data collected from the time of the policy change forward. _We will not notify users by email of any changes to the privacy policy._ Your use of the Site after a policy change has been posted constitutes your acceptance of the policy change. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at the Site periodically.  Do You Have Access to Your Personal and Payment Information?    
Each user will be assigned an account upon registration at our Site. You will be asked to create your own unique login user name and password that can be used to access, update and edit information in your student's account, including Payment Information (e.g., credit card account information), unique identifier information (e.g., customer number or password), transaction information (e.g., dates on which you and student(s) made purchases, amounts and types of purchases), and Personal Information (e.g., name, address, phone number) that we maintain about you.  What Kind of Security Do We Maintain?    
With respect to security: we believe we have taken reasonable steps to protect the privacy of the information we collect in accordance with this policy. We have appropriate security measures in place on our networks and in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our Site. 

However, while we have employed certain security measures, we cannot guarantee the security of all information that we have collected. There are risks associated with transmitting information over the Internet. Users are advised to take steps to protect the security and privacy of their Personal and Payment Information and the login id's and passwords that they create for themselves. 

How to Contact Us    
The Site is operated by Heartland Payment Systems, Inc.

Our postal address is   
570 Devall St., Suite 202  
Auburn, Alabama 36830

We can be reached via email at [support@myschoolbucks.com](mailto:support@myschoolbucks.com)  
or you can reach us by telephone at 1-855-832-5226. 

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above addresses or phone number. 

Effective Date    
This policy is effective as of March 1, 2011
